internetbasedmoms.com 2004-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy**

In today's technological age, Internet Based Moms™ knows you care about how information about you is used and shared and ensures you that any information you provide is used only as necessary to conduct Internet Based Moms™ business.

Please note, your information may be provided to contractors who assist  Internet Based Moms™  in service delivery and it is **_only_** given as needed to perform their contractual duties. Any information you provide here _**will not be** _ given or sold to others, without your express consent or if required by law.

Our newsletter is managed by Intellicontact and subscribers are subject to [ Intellicontact's Privacy Policy](http://www.intellicontact.com/email-privacy.pl). 

We also run a few email groups from time to time and these groups are managed by [Yahoo Groups](http://groups.yahoo.com/). Use of the groups is subject to [ Yahoo's Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/). Please note our group settings do not allow other Yahoo Group members or the general public to see your email address or personal details. However, note that if you reply or post any of the Yahoo Groups we manage, your email address will be viewable to members on the list.

Payments are accepted via PayPal on this website. If you are making a purchase via PayPal, you are subject to [ Pay Pal's Privacy Policy](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside). 

**IP Addresses & Cookies**

Internet Based Moms™' website statistics program does keep track of IP addresses that visit this website. It also uses cookies to determine unique visits from a particular IP. This information is used to collect general statistics about website visitors and does not to track individual behavior.

Our message board uses cookies to keep track of registered members preferences and to provide you with information on posts since your last visit. We do not use this information to track your individual behavior. 

**Message Board Participation**

Please note that information you place in your "profile" on the message boards can be viewed by the general public. If you do not wish to make your email address or personal information public, you can still register for the message boards. You should omit any personal information from the "profile" that you don't want seen by the general public.

By participating in the message boards, you agree that we may reproduce any of your contributions elsewhere on the website, in advertising or in our newsletter. However, we will only publish the information that you make public.

 ** Outside Links**

This website provide links to websites outside of  Internet Based Moms™.  Internet Based Moms™ is not responsible for the content, products, services or privacy policies of these websites.

**Copyright**

All documents, information and logos included on this website are copyright  Internet Based Moms™ 2002-2004, except where noted. Any reproduction of other documents, information and logo is strictly prohibited without the written consent of  Internet Based Moms™.

 ** Terms of Use**

All advice provided on this website is for general informational purposes only.  Internet Based Moms™ is not responsible for any losses that may occur as a result of following this advice. 

Individual services carry their own terms of use. If you are looking to purchase a service from  Internet Based Moms™, please consult the terms of service for that particular service.

 **Policy Changes**

Internet Based Moms™ reserve the right to make changes to these policies and encourage you to review the privacy policy frequently. By continued use of this website, you agree to accept these terms and any changes.
